360-704-0795

evankhaledhosni@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer with a knack for UI/UX. Effective at combining creativity and problem solving to develop user-friendly applications. Always expanding knowledge by keeping abreast of the evolving trends, techniques, and technologies. Earned a bachelor's degree and bootcamp certificate and built professional experience in multiple industries.

SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript/jQuery, HTML5/CSS, C#, Ruby (RGSS1)

Technologies: Node.js, Express.js, React.js, MySQL, MongoDB, API Integration, WebSockets/SocketlO, JSON, Git, Heroku **Applications**: VSCode, Git Bash, Insomnia, Photoshop, Cubase, Pro Tools, Unity, Unreal Engine, Wwise (certified), FMOD, Blender

PROJECTS

Pocket Rascal

pocket-rascal.herokuapp.com github.com/evanhosni/pocket-rascal A virtual pet to take care of, play games

with, and customize.

Technologies: React.js, Matter.js, Material UI, MySQL/Sequelize

Wacky-Wiki

evanhosni.github.io/wackywiki github.com/evanhosni/wackywiki

A 'Mad Libs' style party game using any Wikipedia article.

Technologies: MediaWiki API, Bootstrap,

MetaMemeMarket

meta-meme-market.herokuapp.com github.com/evanhosni/meta-meme-market

A stock market for memes.

Technologies: Express.js, Handlebars, MySQL/Sequelize, Cloudinary

Local Storage

WORK EXPERIENCE

AlphaBest Education - Winston-Salem NC

Full Stack Web Developer (Remote)

• Developing an employee-facing intranet to facilitate communication and efficiency

Evan is a great listener and always adds an element of fun - Brian, Chief Technology Officer

Evan Hosni Audio - Issaquah WA

December 2020 - Present

January 2022 - Present

Sound Designer, Music Composer, Foley Artist, Audio Producer – Since graduating from Berklee, I have worked on two large-scale projects as an independent contractor. My clients and the scope of the projects are listed below:

DMAC Studios / Ultimate Invasion - Palm Beach FL

- Achieved IMDb credit as Sound Designer and Composer for all 8 episodes of Amazon Prime Video series, Ultimate Invasion
- Collaborated with Director Greg LeSar on the creative direction of the show's audio and met time-sensitive deadlines

Green Mouse Academy - Palm Beach FL

- Produced audio for 100+ children's educational videos to date
- Collaborated with a team of editors to complete projects on time and developed strategies to streamline workflow

Evan masters the art of storytelling through audio. He was born to do this - Greg LeSar, Director/Writer - Ultimate Invasion

Evan, you are a talented professional and an absolute pleasure to work with - Shane VanderKooi, CEO - Green Mouse Academy

Guitar Center - Tukwila WA, Redmond WA

July 2015 - March 2021

Repair Technician - 2015 - 2019

Area Specialist - 2019 - 2021

- · Cultivated a dedicated customer following by focusing on the customer experience
- Recognized by D'Addario Musical Instruments as a top performer in 2017
- Developed promotional programs to engage repair techs in incremental selling activities

Evan is a god among repair techs, and an overall cool guy - Owen, Customer

EDUCATION

Berklee College of Music - Bachelor of Professional Studies

June 2016 - December 2020

Interdisciplinary Music Studies - Focus in Sound Design (Dean's List - six consecutive quarters)

Evan, another awesome soundscape! Man, I love hearing what you put together...really excited about this – Will Robertson, Professor

University of Washington Coding Boot Camp - Certificate of Completion

August 2021 - December 2021

300+ hour course on dynamic full stack coding curriculum

Awarded Best UI/UX for all three student projects as well as People's Choice for 'Wacky-Wiki'

linkedin.com/in/evanhosni - evanhosni.com - github.com/evanhosni